GÜRKAN HÜRAY

SECURITY & RISK PROFESSIONAL



CONTACT

+420 605 955 141

gurkanhuray@gmail.com

Prague, Czechia

SOCIAL



linkedin.com/in/gurkanhuray

PRO SKILLS

IRAM SGOP

profile for my proficiency.



PROFILE

Experienced Security and Risk Professional who worked in multi-national companies with a demonstrated history of working in the technology, finance, paper-and-forest products sectors. Skilled in many invaluable areas as described in the 'Pro Skills' section. Participated in many different initiatives, including for auditing purposes in Japan, Romania and Ukraine. Has a solid working background in internationally recognised standards and frameworks, including ISF's IRAM, SGOP - NIST's CSF. A solid contributor to the implementation of risk and control frameworks. Leading the ISMS program.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Stora Enso Czechia

Nov 2019 - Present

Senior Manager, Information and Cyber Security - Risk Jan 2019 - Nov 2019 Information Security and Risk Manager

- · Leading development work to improve the quality of Information Security and Cyber Security in the organisation.
- · Supporting the CISO in designing, implementing and maintaining an ISMS and enhancing the effectiveness of risk management and related IS governance processes.
- Supporting business process owners and service managers in the execution of the Information Risk Management process.

2015 - 2018 Nationale-Nederlanden Turkey

Senior Information Risk Management Specialist

- Maintaining the IT Risk Framework and its associated controls and reporting. It includes Risk Identification, Assessment and Evaluation, Risk Response, Risk Monitoring, IS Control Design and Implementation, IS Control Monitoring and Maintenance, IS Policies/Governance and Compliance, BCM and DRP
- · Assuring overall information technology risk, keeping an active view, and reporting on the actual, mitigated and residual risk in the technology organisation.

IBM Turkey 2010 - 2015

IT Security Specialist

- · Involving in internal/corporate audits against auditors as process owner of various security domains (based on internationally recognised frameworks/standards).
- · Leading implementation of third-party tools such as CyberArk to address specific security-related concerns.
- Acting as an SME for the EMEA region to provide best practices.

2009 - 2010 **IBM Turkey**

Technical & Customer Services Representative

· Supporting clients & employees in all technical deliveries.

CERTIFICATION | CISM

EDUCATION

2021 - 2023

University of Essex Online, UK

Industrial Electronics, Associate Degree

Cybersecurity, MSc

2004 - 2007 Afyon Kocatepe University, Turkey

A list of complete skill set can be found in the LinkedIn